<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meetings and appraisals on Notebook</title>
    <link>https://cdu-data-science-team.github.io/the-cdu-way/docs/meetings_appraisals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meetings and appraisals on Notebook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://cdu-data-science-team.github.io/the-cdu-way/docs/meetings_appraisals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Etiquette</title>
      <link>https://cdu-data-science-team.github.io/the-cdu-way/docs/meetings_appraisals/etiquette/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cdu-data-science-team.github.io/the-cdu-way/docs/meetings_appraisals/etiquette/</guid>
      <description>Diary management #   Put meetings in your diary, including personal things that happen during daytime (you can use personal) It should always be as up to date as possible but at least make sure when the week starts before our team meeting it is accurate as can be Everyone in the team should be able to view everyone else&amp;rsquo;s diary Accept or decline meetings. Use Tentative sparingly- seeing tentative across the diary all the time is confusing Select the appropriate busy/free status with the consideration how it impacts teams (out of office is good for showing away from computer for example for personal calls etc)  Booking meetings #   Where known consider people’s working patterns Check diaries, most people you can see some free/busy options Some people’s diaries are particularly chaotic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regular meetings</title>
      <link>https://cdu-data-science-team.github.io/the-cdu-way/docs/meetings_appraisals/regular_meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cdu-data-science-team.github.io/the-cdu-way/docs/meetings_appraisals/regular_meetings/</guid>
      <description>This section concerns regular meetings, which comprise:
As a small team we have a few regular meetings
 Stand Up: Every Monday 0930-1030 we meet, have a general chat, and then discuss our plans for the week, this allows for us to understand the issues, appreciate what people are up to and an opportunity to offer advice/support. Very informal Code Review: Fortnightly Friday 1100-1200 there is a meeting called Code Review but is very loosely a code review as sometimes we have general discussions around approaching a problem, may be a problem with code you want support with, could be showing off some snazzy code or anything that getting a quorum on is beneficial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subsection 3</title>
      <link>https://cdu-data-science-team.github.io/the-cdu-way/docs/meetings_appraisals/subection_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cdu-data-science-team.github.io/the-cdu-way/docs/meetings_appraisals/subection_3/</guid>
      <description>Subsection 3 #  This is a subsection of chapter one</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
